45 years old Miss Estella Mutale has come all the way from Zambia to The SCOAN
with the problem of HIV/AIDS Positive 1.
This is the medical report from the Ministry of Health, Ndola Central Hospital in Zambia,
testing and confirming that she has HIV/AIDS Positive 1.
She has come believing that Jesus Christ will heal her in His Holy name.
Let's hear from her.
My name is Miss Estella Mutale, I came from Zambia.
I am 45 years old.
I have HIV/AIDS Positive 1.
Tell us the name of the hospital that tested and confirmed that you have HIV/AIDS Positive 1.
Ndola Central Hospital, Zambia.
I feel weak, I have no appetite and have painful headaches.
What is the cause of this HIV/AIDS Positive 1 in your life?
Adultery and fornication.
For how long have you been having this problem of HIV/AIDS Positive 1?
Eight years.
Now that you are here at The SCOAN, what do you believe that God Almighty would do for you?
I believe I will be healed, in the name of Jesus.
Healing Time
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministering prayer and healing in Jesus' name
She is my wife.
What have you done to her?
What sickness have you given to her ?
I gave her HIV/AIDS and fibroids.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I gave her skin disease.
What have you done to her marriage?
No marriage. She is my wife.
What have you done to her career?
No career and business failure.
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministering prayer and healing in Jesus' name
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Set Free In Jesus' Name
To God be the glory.
She is free.
Testimony Continues
Hallelujah! You are welcome, in the name of Jesus Christ.
Please tell us your name and where you are from.
My name is Miss Estella Mutale, I come from Zambia.
My testimony goes like this:
In 2008, I started feeling strange - rashes all over my body, sicknesses, everything in my body.
I lost appetite.
I saw rashes all over my body.
In 2008, I went to the hospital, and I was tested to have HIV/AIDS Positive 1.
I went back home and told my family about it.
My son introduced me to Emmanuel TV.
Hallelujah !
So, we can understand where our sister is coming from.
She had the problem of HIV/AIDS Positive 1.
We just want you to lay a bit more emphasis on how this problem affected your life.
How did you feel when the doctors told you that you had HIV/AIDS?
I felt bad. I was lying down throughout the day and the night
because the doctor had told me that there was no cure for this disease.
I was afraid that I would die at any moment.
What were the symptoms you had over the years because of this HIV/AIDS?
Fornication and adultery.
You mean that was the cause?
Yes.
But what we were asking is: How did HIV affect you and your health?
What were those problems you had because of HIV?
It was affecting me.
I was a business lady. I couldn't do anything.
I was always bedridden.
It caused me dejection, and I had the spirit of fear.
If I went out and took a bus, a voice would be telling me that I would die.
Then, my son introduced me to Emmanuel TV.
I started watching Emmanuel TV 24/7.
One fateful day, I saw a lady from Botswana testifying of being healed from HIV/AIDS.
So, I was encouraged and my faith started growing.
I decided to come to The SCOAN in 2015.
The man of God prayed for me.
Two days after Prophet T.B. Joshua had prayed for me, everything - rashes, sicknesses - disappeared.
Hallelujah! Put your hands together for Jesus!
We can see on the screen, the moment our sister received prayer from Prophet T.B. Joshua,
in the name of Jesus Christ.
That evil spirit that was behind her sickness of HIV/AIDS started manifesting.
During that time of deliverance, what was your experience?
I am okay, everything (of HIV) disappeared.
Then, I went back home to my country Zambia.
In January 2016, I went back to the same hospital.
Which hospital was that?
University Teaching Hospital in Zambia.
They tested me to be HIV/AIDS negative.
Hallelujah! Put your hands together for Jesus!
Truly, with God, nothing is impossible. Amen!
If you know God Almighty is going to turn your impossibility into possibility,
put your hands together for Jesus!
Hallelujah!
Since you were re-tested (HIV) negative by the grace of God, after the prayer from the man of God,
how is your life now and how are you feeling?
I feel very happy.
I am okay!
What about the rashes you used to have? What about your job? Have you gone back to work?
Everything disappeared, I am okay.
Put your hands together for Jesus once again!
Have you gone back to your job? And how is your business now, after your healing?
During that sickness of HIV/AIDS, I had the spirit of setback, rejection,
everything I put my hands on would not work.
But now, after the deliverance, how have things changed in your business?
Everything has changed.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus once again!
We can see some documents on the board next to you.
Can you explain to us one by one what they are?
The first one is the HIV/AIDS Positive 1 test result: Confirmed to be HIV/Positive 1.
After the prayer from the man of God, I went back to the hospital and I was tested to be HIV/AIDS negative.
I was tested negative on everything.
Hallelujah! Put your hands together for Jesus Christ, the Master Healer!
This was in 2016. In 2017, the HIV/AIDS test result also came out negative.
Hallelujah! God is good, all the time!
We want to hear your word of advice to people watching you all over the world.
People all over the world, especially to single ladies like me, my advice is that you should stay away from sin.
Stay faithful to God.
Secondly, keep watching Emmanuel TV.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
Madam, we thank God Almighty for this wonderful healing that God has done in your life.
We encourage you to continue to make God's Word the standard for your life.
And this healing will remain permanent, in Jesus' name.